练习 1-45：固定短语故事《卖火柴的小女孩》。下面这个故事只包含固定短语。
Exercise 1-45, Set Phrase Story, The Little Match Girl. The following story
重读每个短语的第一个词。
contains only set phrases. Stress the first word of each phrase. The little
match girl was out in a snowstorm. Her feet were like ice cubes and her
fingertips had frostbite. She hadn't sold any matches since daybreak and she had a
stomach ache from the hunger pangs, but her stepmother would beat her with a
broomstick if she came home with an empty coin purse. Looking into the bright living
rooms, she saw Christmas trees and warm fireplaces.
Out on the snowbank, she lit a match and saw the image of a grand dinner table of
food before her. As the matchstick burned, the illusion slowly faded. She lit another
one and saw a room full of happy family members. On the last match, her
grandmother came down and carried her home. In the morning, the passers-by saw
the little match girl. She had frozen during the nighttime, but she had a smile
on her face.
对比描述性短语和固定短语。现在我们有两种主要语调
Contrasting a description and a set phrase. We now have two main intonation
模式：第一个词重读和第二个词重读。在下面的练习中，
patterns, first word stress and second word stress. In the following exercise,
我们会对比这两种模式。
we'll contrast the two.